Guide to the Charles and Shirley Weiss Collection of Opera Ephemera, 1951-2003 RL.11139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1991 June 29 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1992 February 13 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1994 November 14 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 January 28 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 July 6 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Western Opera Theater, Chapel Hill, NC), 1995 November 8 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 October 19 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1998 February 11 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1998 May 2 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1998 May 12 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 November 7 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1999 July 26 (Box 2)
- Le Nozze di Figaro (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2001 March 20 (Box 2)
- Oberon (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1988 June 11 (Box 2)
- Oedipus (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1991 July 27 (Box 2)
- Oedipus Rex (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 December 19 (Box 2)
- Oedipus Tex (Opera Southwest, Albuquerque, NM), 1996 July 19 (Box 2)
- Of Mice and Men (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1983 October 19 (Box 2)
- Of Mice and Men (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1985 June 7 (Box 2)
- Of Mice and Men (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1997 August 22 (Box 2)
- Of Mice and Men (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2001 October 28 (Box 2)
- Oni Musume (Japanese Opera Ashi, Seattle, WA), 1989 September 2 (Box 2)
- Opheus in the Underworld (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1983 August 9 (Box 2)
- Opheus in the Underworld (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1985 August 5 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (Gran Teatro del Liceo, Barcelona, Spain), 1963 December 21 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1984 June 23 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1994 February 27 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 May 18 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1996 January 16 (Box 2)
- Orfeo ed Euridice (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 October 16 (Box 2)
- L'Orione (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1983 August 17 (Box 2)
- Orlando (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1986 October 24 (Box 2)
- Orlando Furioso (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 December 9 (Box 2)
- L'Ormindo (Carolina Baroque Opera, Chapel Hill, NC), 1977 March 31 (Box 2)
- L'Ormindo (The Curtis Institute of Music Opera Theatre, Philadelphia, PA), 1997 April 27 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 February 24 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 October 7 (Box 2)
- Otello (Opera Colorado, Denver, CO), 1983 April 9 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 February 7 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 September 25 (Box 2)
- Otello (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1992 October 5 (Box 2)
- Otello (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 November 15 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 April 9 (Box 2)
- Otello (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 October 18 (Box 2)
- Otello (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 October 13 (Box 2)
- Otello (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1999 June 26 (Box 2)
- Otello (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 March 8 (Box 2)
- Otello (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2002 October 9 (Box 2)
- Pagliacci (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 January 28 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 November 10 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1987 November 1 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 March 7 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 November 12 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1996 September 14 (Box 3)
- Pagliacci (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 November 16 (Box 3)
- Parade (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 March 13 (Box 3)
- Parade (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 11 (Box 3)
- Parade (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 March 16 (Box 3)
- Pariser Leben (Volksoper, Vienna, Austria), 1982 December 25 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 April 14 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 April 8 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1986 October 22 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1990 June 2 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1992 February 21 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 April 11 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 November 15 (Box 3)
- Parsifal (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 April 10 (Box 3)
- Partenope (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 September 19 (Box 3)
- The Passion of Jonathan Wade (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1991 April 21 (Box 3)
- The Passion of Jonathan Wade (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1996 March 5 (Box 3)
- Paul Bunyan (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1984 June 22 (Box 3)
- Paul Bunyan (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 April 9 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 March 28 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1993 January 27 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (English National Opera, London, England), 1994 March 30 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1998 February 10 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1999 June 24 (Box 3)
- Les Pecheurs de Perles (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 2000 January 25 (Box 3)
- Pelleas et Melisande (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1992 November 23 (Box 3)
- Pelleas et Melisande (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1993 March 17 (Box 3)
- Pelleas et Melisande (Los Angeles Music Center Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1995 February 10 (Box 3)
- Pelleas et Melisande (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 November 20 (Box 3)
- Pelleas et Melisande (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 April 13 (Box 3)
- Peter Grimes (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 November 26 (Box 3)
- Peter Grimes (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 November 19 (Box 3)
- Peter Grimes (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1990 June 23 (Box 3)
- Peter Grimes (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1997 October 3 (Box 3)
- Peter Grimes (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 November 17 (Box 3)
- Il Pirata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 November 9 (Box 3)
- The Pirates of Penzance (Durham Savoyards, Ltd., Durham, NC), 1978 April 21 (Box 3)
- The Pirates of Penzance (NY Shakespeare Festival Production, New York, NY), 1982 April 10 (Box 3)
- Platee (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1987 May 24 (Box 3)
- Platee (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 April 11 (Box 3)
- Pomme d'Api (Theatre Nationale Opera de Paris, Paris, France), 1983 December 31 (Box 3)
- Porgy and Bess (Duke University, Durham, NC), 1981 April 8 (Box 3)
- Porgy and Bess (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 February 6 (Box 3)
- Porgy and Bess (The Catfish Row Company, Charleston, SC), 1985 October 20 (Box 3)
- Porgy and Bess (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 September 30 (Box 3)
- The Postman Always Rings Twice (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1989 January 26 (Box 3)
- The Power of Xingu (The UNC Opera Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC), 1998 April 14 (Box 3)
- Prince Igor (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1994 September 28 (Box 3)
- Prince Igor (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1996 September 18 (Box 3)
- Prince Igor (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 May 9 (Box 3)
- Prince Igor (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2001 February 11 (Box 3)
- Princess Ida (Durham Savoyards, Ltd., Durham, NC), 1975 April 26 (Box 3)
- Der Prinz von Homburg (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1995 May 28 (Box 3)
- Le Prohpete (Metropolitan Opera Tour, Vienna, VA), 1977 June 7 (Box 3)
- The Protagonist (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 July 31 (Box 3)
- I Puritani (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 27 (Box 3)
- I Puritani (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 December 6 (Box 3)
- I Puritani (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 April 13 (Box 3)
- I Puritani (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 November 27 (Box 3)
- I Puritani (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 December 29 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1977 May 29 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1982 November 12 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1989 March 5 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 November 26 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 October 26 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 April 15 (Box 3)
- The Queen of Spades (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 October 25 (Box 3)
- Radamisto (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2000 June 22 (Box 3)
- The Rake's Progress (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1982 December 29 (Box 3)
- The Rake's Progress (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1985 January 25 (Box 3)
- The Rake's Progress (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1994 October 22 (Box 3)
- The Rake's Progress (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1996 July 26 (Box 3)
- The Rake's Progress (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 December 6 (Box 3)
- The Rape of Lucretia (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1996 June 22 (Box 3)
- Rappaccini's Daughter (The Minnesota Opera Company, St. Paul, MN), 1983 September 3 (Box 3)
- Rappaccini's Daughter (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1994 March 8 (Box 3)
- Rasputin (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1988 September 17 (Box 3)
- The Red Line (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 April 30 (Box 3)
- Renard (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1986 May 30 (Box 3)
- Requiem Variations (Opera Omaha, Omaha, NB), 1994 June 11 (Box 3)
- Resurrection (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1999 April 28 (Box 3)
- The Return of Ulysses (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1997 May 6 (Box 3)
- The Return of Ulysses (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2001 November 4 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 November 12 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 March 3 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 July 11 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 December 19 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1984 November 23 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1988 September 21 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 March 25 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 November 18 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 March 1 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 March 14 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 November 2 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 September 16 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1998 May 15 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 November 14 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2000 June 30 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 October 24 (Box 3)
- Rigoletto (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 September 12 (Box 3)
- Rinaldo (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 November 4 (Box 3)
- Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 December 8 (Box 3)
- Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 April 11 (Box 3)
- Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 December 9 (Box 3)
- Rise and Fall of the City of Mahagonny (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1998 November 20 (Box 3)
- Roberto Devereux (Festival International d'Art Lyrique, Aix-en-Provence, France), 1977 July 25 (Box 3)
- Roberto Devereux (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 October 4 (Box 3)
- Roman Fever (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1993 June 13 (Box 3)
- Roman Fever (UNC-CH Dept of Music, Chapel Hill, NC), 1996 September 29 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1981 December 11 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 February 22 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1986 July 12 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 December 6 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1987 November 13 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1993 January 16 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 November 15 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 April 8 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 February 23 (Box 3)
- Romeo et Juliette (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1999 May 21 (Box 3)
- Romulus Hunt (The Opera Company of NC, Raleigh, NC), 1999 November 15 (Box 3)
- La Rondine (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1985 November 9 (Box 3)
- La Rondine (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1995 March 23 (Box 3)
- La Rondine (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1996 June 22 (Box 3)
- La Rondine (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 March 17 (Box 3)
- Rose de Noel (Opera de Nice, Nice, France ), 1977 December 23 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Royal Opera House, London, England), 1963 December 31 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Bayerische Staatsoper Nationaltheater Munchen, Munich, Germany), 1977 July 15 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 December 17 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 April 23 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1982 December 22 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 November 24 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 November 8 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 March 2 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1992 January 6 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1992 July 25 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Minnesota Orchestra, New York, NY), 1993 February 7 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 June 27 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1995 January 13 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1995 May 26 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1995 June 10 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1996 October 4 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (Opera National de Paris, Paris, France), 1997 November 29 (Box 3)
- Der Rosenkavalier (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 December 7 (Box 3)
- Le Rossignol (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 December 19 (Box 3)
- Ruddigore (Durham Savoyards, Ltd., Durham, NC), 1979 April 20 (Box 3)
- Ruddigore (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1988 January 3 (Box 3)
- Rusalka (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 November 18 (Box 3)
- Ruslan and Lyudmila (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 September 22 (Box 3)
- Ruslan and Lyudmila (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 May 8 (Box 3)
- Le Sacre du Printemps (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 December 19 (Box 3)
- Saint Francois d'Assise (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2002 October 10 (Box 3)
- The Saint of Bleecker Street (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1986 May 23 (Box 3)
- The Saint of Bleecker Street (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 January 26 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1979 August 11 (Box 3)
- Salome (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 March 14 (Box 3)
- Salome (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1982 October 17 (Box 3)
- Salome (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1987 May 22 (Box 3)
- Salome (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1990 June 7 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1990 November 1 (Box 3)
- Salome (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 December 1 (Box 3)
- Salome (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 June 26 (Box 3)
- Salome (Royal Opera House, London, England), 1995 March 15 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 July 22 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 August 18 (Box 3)
- Salome (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 March 23 (Box 3)
- Salome (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1998 February 17 (Box 3)
- Salome (Opera Colorado, Denver, CO), 1998 May 1 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1998 July 29 (Box 3)
- Salome (English National Opera, London, England), 1999 April 1 (Box 3)
- Salome (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2002 April 15 (Box 3)
- Salome (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 October 20 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1981 October 23 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 April 3 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 February 24 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 March 14 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 November 10 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 October 7 (Box 3)
- Samson et Dalila (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 October 9 (Box 3)
- Satyagraha (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1987 October 17 (Box 3)
- Savage Land (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 January 26 (Box 3)
- Die Schweigsame Frau (Glyndebourne Festival Opera, Glyndebourne, England), 1977 July 13 (Box 3)
- Die Schweigsame Frau (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1987 July 29 (Box 3)
- Die Schweigsame Frau (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1991 July 20 (Box 3)
- The Secret of Susanna (UNC-CH Dept of Music, Chapel Hill, NC), 1998 April 14 (Box 3)
- The Seduction of a Lady (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1987 February 12 (Box 3)
- The Seduction of a Lady (The Academy of Vocal Arts, Philadelphia, PA), 1997 April 29 (Box 3)
- The Selfish Giant (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 26 (Box 3)
- Semele (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1995 February 6 (Box 3)
- Semele (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1997 August 7 (Box 3)
- Semele (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 November 7 (Box 3)
- Semiramide (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 September 20 (Box 3)
- Semiramide (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 December 22 (Box 3)
- Semiramide (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 November 20 (Box 3)
- La Serva Padrona (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1984 May 26 (Box 3)
- The Seven Deadly Sins (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 April 4 (Box 3)
- The Seven Deadly Sins (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 September 19 (Box 3)
- Shining Brow (Madison Opera, Madison, WI), 1993 April 21 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 24 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1982 August 6 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 June 5 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1986 August 13 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 February 12 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 May 4 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 January 24 (Box 3)
- Siegfried (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 2001 August 24 (Box 3)
- The Silver River (Sante Fe Chamber Music Festival, Santa Fe, NM), 1997 July 27 (Box 3)
- The Silver River (Sante Fe Chamber Music Festival, Santa Fe, NM), 1997 July 28 (Box 3)
- The Silver River (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2000 May 28 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1979 November 24 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1980 June 11 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1984 July 1 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 April 17 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 March 22 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 January 26 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 October 10 (Box 3)
- Simon Boccanegra (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 November 11 (Box 3)
- The Singing Child (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1993 June 1 (Box 3)
- The Sinking of the Rainbow Warrior (Sydney Festival, Sydney, Australia), 1997 January 15 (Box 3)
- Sly (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 March 15 (Box 3)
- Sly (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 April 8 (Box 3)
- Die Soldaten (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1991 October 17 (Box 3)
- A Song in the Wind (Opera Southwest, Albuquerque, NM), 1996 July 19 (Box 3)
- La Sonnambula (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1980 May 23 (Box 3)
- La Sonnambula (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1984 December 1 (Box 3)
- La Sonnambula (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1988 October 7 (Box 3)
- The Sorcerer (Durham Savoyards, Ltd., Durham, NC), 1977 April 22 (Box 3)
- The Sorrows of Young Werther (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1992 August 1 (Box 3)
- Soul Gone Home (Mallarme Chamber Players, Durham, NC), 2002 May 4 (Box 3)
- Soul Gone Home (Mallarme Chamber Players, Durham, NC), 2002 May 5 (Box 3)
- Stiffelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 21 (Box 3)
- Stiffelio (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1995 September 19 (Box 3)
- La Straniera (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1989 May 26 (Box 3)
- Street Scene (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1990 September 15 (Box 3)
- A Streetcar Named Desire (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 September 23 (Box 3)
- Suor Angelica (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 0199 May 28 (Box 3)
- Suor Angelica (The NC Lyric Opera, Inc., Durham, NC), 1976 May 25 (Box 3)
- Suor Angelica (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 October 30 (Box 3)
- Suor Angelica (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 September 30 (Box 3)
- Suor Angelica (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 September 25 (Box 3)
- Susannah (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 October 24 (Box 3)
- Susannah (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 November 1 (Box 3)
- Susannah (UNC-CH Opera Theater Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC), 1994 April 6 (Box 3)
- Susannah (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 April 16 (Box 3)
- Susannah (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 November 12 (Box 3)
- Taanhauser (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 January 30 (Box 3)
- Taanhauser (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 11 (Box 3)
- Taanhauser (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1984 March 10 (Box 3)
- Taanhauser (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 January 31 (Box 3)
- Taanhauser (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 October 20 (Box 3)
- Il Tabarro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 October 30 (Box 3)
- Il Tabarro (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 September 26 (Box 3)